[{"answer": "Well, that's an understatement, Piers, to say pretty good.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Has he sealed the deal yet?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, he's been consistent in focusing on Barack Obama.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Is that going to be the consistent strategy going forward?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "Well, Ron Paul and Mitt Romney don't agree on many things.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Are you taking him seriously now as a possible threat to win the nomination?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, it's inaccurate and unfair.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "How do you answer the charge that Mitt Romney is a vulture?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think we say -- you're saying we had money.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Are you concerned that one of your opponents now has the kind of financial muscle to play dirty in the way that you have?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Well, we're dangerous to the status quo.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "But can you move from dangerous to electable, do you think?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Well, there are two things that should bring all Republicans together, and that is, one is realizing that, you know, the media will pull some \"gotcha\" statements from time to time and take things out of context.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "Why did he stick his neck out like that?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "It's going to get more serious, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "From the people.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "And finally and quickly, where does he get his energy from?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "Big victory for Mitt Romney, 39, 40 percent, very, very impressive in a crowded field like that and from his perspective, the two candidates he probably feared the most, Rick Santorum and Newt Gingrich, they did not do well coming in fourth and fifth.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "What do you think we've ended up at?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Almost forget the candidates for a minute.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "John King, the big question, I guess, is of all the other runners and writers, have any of them got it in them to actually challenge Mitt Romney in South Carolina and going forward?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Well, how can you claim you're stronger if you keep losing to the candidate you call weak or freak?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "And tell you, we had a spirited debate earlier about whether it was to the party's advantage, the Republicans, to have an extended battle.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "It's hard to make that argument, isn't it?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "There are those who argue that, who believes that.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "It goes on, could Romney not become a more formidable opponent?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "He's going to go for it, isn't he, through the super PAC?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "This is going to be really difficult.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Who's going to win this argument?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Here's the difference between Iowa and South Carolina.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Could he take some of that time and some of that voting away from Mitt Romney because they (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "He's not -- it isn't a done deal yet.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "If Mitt Romney wins in South Carolina, is he basically the nominee?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Well, I would agree with that but I would think the momentum would be so much behind him.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Erin?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Done deal.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "David, three out of three, a done deal?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "John?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Well, we didn't compete in New Hampshire so it doesn't surprise us that our score there was a bit on the low side.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Being in the 1 percent is the last place you want to find yourself, isn't it?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "Well, the fact is that there's a lot going to happen in the next two weeks in South Carolina.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "What are you going to do to turn around your fortunes given the fairly (INAUDIBLE) state you're in at the moment?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think so.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "For any candidate to actually seriously challenge him for the nomination, isn't it?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Well, actually, the last three or four debates I think we performed at a rather high level.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Why have you found the debates such a struggle?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Well, there's a real difference between a venture capitalist and a vulture capitalist.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Because if Mitt Romney now wins the nomination, haven't you just landed Barack Obama a perfect stick to beat him with?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Well, I think you said the magic words, if I meet that point, which is not in our game plan at all.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "What is the realistic endgame for you if you reach that point?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Well, no doubt about it, Piers.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "What's your assessment?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Well, this is South Carolina.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "Or is it good for the party?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "ONNELLY: You know, I really think, Piers, that a long, drawn-out battle is not necessarily a bad thing because it engages people nationwide.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "I mean is it a good thing to wrap it up early or can you see the merits of a good old tussle?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Well, you know, we are fiercely evangelical.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Is that going to be a problem for him, do you think?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Nobody.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Who are you endorsing right now?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Well, he's playing a very good game of defense when he has a lot of money working to his benefit and he's playing defense.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "And you can dismiss him but what more can he be doing than he is doing?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Can I get behind this guy the way that I got behind John McCain?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Well, he is winning.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "I mean he's not doing badly for somebody that everyone else says they're not very enthusiastic about?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Oh, my father never got involved in contested primaries for very good reasons and, in fact, would support the nominee of the party.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "But who do you think he would have been steering to?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Well, what's happened over the last few months is -- we've had a focus on the Republican Party and the Republican candidates with the media focusing on the Republican Party and what does it stand for and it's been a diversion from what does Barack Obama stand for and what has he been able to do.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Barack Obama's got it all to do, hasn't he?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think you know me, Piers Morgan.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "So what do you think of the new politics where everyone just whacks everybody else?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "He didn't believe Republicans should do this to each other, did he?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "I think it was very disingenuous.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "The fact that he's now turning mean, I guess, is the story because he tried to present himself as the new Newt, the nice Newt, the saintly Newt and it didn't work and now he's going to go back to the way perhaps a more traditional Newt would have behaved which is when an opponent whacks him he's going to whack him back, isn't he?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Has he won?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Not much of a chance.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "Has he still got a chance do you think?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "It's all going to Romney.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Where's the smart money going now?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "There's no question it's the latter.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "And the other question I want to put to you, if you're Barack Obama, would you rather know who the nominee is now or are you happy to watch the Republicans scrap it out for a few more months?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "He's the favorite.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "Do both of you agree Mitt Romney at the moment looks like a shoo-in?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "Ninety percent.", "docId": "120110pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "I'd say upward of 90 percent?", "qSentId": 636}]